Christmas Incorporated is a tv movie, drama film directed by Jonathan Wright.
Sometimes, life just seems to hand you exactly what you
need – particularly at Christmastime.
Riley is scraping bottom when she miraculously lands a job
with a wealthy New York City entrepreneur.
He’s a bad-boy socialite type who is poised to play Scrooge by closing one of his
factories just before Christmas, which would devastate an entire town.
It’s left to Riley to talk him out of it and turn him
into a man of virtue rather than shame.
Riley Vance, played by Shenae Grimes-Beech.
William Young, played by Steve Lund.
Mayor Martin Keegan, played by Ron Lea.
Amanda Sage, played by Jane Moffat.
Emily Lamb, played by Miranda Millar.
Piper, played by Hannah Spear.
Black Christmas is a 1974 Canadian slasher film produced and
directed by Bob Clark, and written by Roy Moore.
It stars Olivia Hussey, Keir Dullea, Margot Kidder, and John Saxon.
The story follows a group of sorority sisters who receive threatening phone calls and are
eventually stalked and murdered by a killer during the Christmas season.
Inspired by the urban legend "the babysitter and the man upstairs" and a series of murders that took place in the
Westmount neighbourhood of Montreal, Quebec, Moore wrote the screenplay under the title Stop Me.
The filmmakers made numerous alterations to the script, primarily the
shifting to a university setting with young adult characters.
It was shot in Toronto in 1974 on an estimated budget of $686,000.
The film was released in Canada on October 11, 1974
by Ambassador Film Distributors.
Warner Bros.
released the film in the United States in May 1975 under the alternate title Silent Night, Evil Night, though this
title was retracted and the film was reissued under its original title beginning August 6, 1975.
The film went on to gross $4,053,000 worldwide.
Upon its release, Black Christmas received mixed reviews, but it has since received critical
re-appraisal, with film historians noting it for being one of the earliest slasher films.
It is also praised for its influence on John Carpenter's Halloween (1978).
Aside from it earning a cult following since its release, a
novelization written by Lee Hays was published in 1976.
It is the first film in the Black Christmas series, being
followed by two remakes in 2006 and  2019.
The film explores themes of mistaken identity,
co-workers relationship, toy factory, christmas.
The tone is emotional.